<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://acegiftsplus.ca/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://acegiftsplus.ca/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://acegiftsplus.ca/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>Ace Gifts Plus - News</title>
  <updated>2014-08-10T20:46:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Ace Gifts Plus</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://acegiftsplus.ca/blogs/news/15734011-what-is-the-ace-advantage</id>
    <published>2014-08-10T20:46:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-06-20T21:11:37-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://acegiftsplus.ca/blogs/news/15734011-what-is-the-ace-advantage"/>
    <title>What is the Ace Advantage?</title>
    <author>
      <name>Gajender Kalra</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0" align="center" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td align="center" class="title2"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0611/4257/files/welcome2_c19bdaad-66b1-4e9e-b0f0-5222a68695a4_medium.jpg?429"></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left" class="body">
<div align="justify">
<p>We thank you for taking the time to familiarize yourself with our company, our values and our fine products and services.</p>
<p>On this page, we invite you to explore our company’s philosophy, be familiar with our business strategy and understand what we truly stand for.</p>
</div>
<div align="justify"></div>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center" class="title"> </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center" class="title"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0611/4257/files/history_medium.jpg?420"></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left" class="body">
<div align="justify">Established in 1992, we are a large perfume retailer, domiciled in the Greater Toronto Region. Our reach and clientele extends beyond borders, with customers ranging locally to customers spanning across Eastern and Western Canada.</div>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center"> </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center" class="title">
<img alt="" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0611/4257/files/mission_medium.jpg?421"><br><a name="mission" id="mission"></a>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left" class="body">
<div align="justify">To provide exceptional value and quality service, and deliver substantial value added savings to all customers as Canada’s leading wholesaler and retailer of authentic brand name<br>perfumes and cosmetics.</div>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center"> </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center" class="title">
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0611/4257/files/strategy_large.jpg?422"><br><a name="strategy" id="strategy"></a>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left" class="body">
<div align="justify">Our mission, as simplistic as it sounds in writing is something we take very seriously. To ensure our every action is aligned with our mission, we aim to add value to our clientele in every possible way. We hold desirable inventory levels at competitive prices and strive to ensure unrivalled customer service with our industry expertise and genuine desire to develop lasting relationships. <br><br>Together with our values, fine reputation and industry experience, we are confident that <br>Ace Gifts Plus has more than what you want…<strong><em><br>we are what you’ve been looking for!</em></strong>
</div>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center"> </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center" class="title">
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0611/4257/files/corevalue_large.jpg?426"><br><a name="value" id="value"></a>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0611/4257/files/corevaluepic_large.jpg?427"></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td height="10" align="center"></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center"> </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left" class="body">
<div align="justify">There's a reason thousands of loyal customer continue to choose Ace Gifts Plus as their number one choice for their fragrance needs. It's because our values are tied to the well being of our customers. We strive to ensure each customer receives the product they desire and the <br>quality service they deserve!</div>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left"> </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left">
<p align="justify" class="body"><strong class="title3">Integrity and honesty in what we do</strong><br>We believe every successful relationship rests on trust, honesty and respect. And we respect our customers' fundamental right to obtain uncompromised quality products. Since we have been trading for over 16 years, our customers know that we are consistent and reliable. We source all of our products from reputable suppliers that we know and trust. Being in the business for such a long period of time, all our customers know and have the confidence that we only trade in genuine products and maintain integrity in every aspect of our business. We take pride in our +3,000 brand name items, all of which are authentic and warehoused with due care. <br>We have zero tolerance for fake or diluted items.</p>
<p align="justify" class="body"><strong class="title3">Our customer-first approach</strong><br>Our customers are our most valuable asset and we understand that our success is tied to their well-being. Thus, we are committed to ensuring our customer's needs are met at every stage of the business transaction. This need-first approach is our company's differentiating aspect. Half the service areas in the city don't cater to the customer but make the customer cater to them. At Ace, we want our customers to be satisfied and endeavor to keep them more like friends. If there is a product that we do not have in stock or is warehoused at one of our retail locations, we will ensure to get it to the customer on a timely basis. We pride the excellence in our service!</p>
<p align="justify" class="body"><strong class="title3">Long-term relationships</strong><br>Nothing makes us more delighted than seeing our loyal customers return, even if its just to say "Hi!" At Ace, you will find a warm and welcoming staff ready to serve you and to provide you the best service in the country! We aim to maintain this close relationship and develop friendships with our valued customers during every step of the purchasing decision process. It's no surprise then, that we still have returning customers from near and far since our inception in 1992!</p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center"> </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center" class="title">
<img alt="" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0611/4257/files/our_large.jpg?424"><br><a name="4" id="4"></a>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left">
<p align="justify" class="body style3"><strong>“Delivering authentic top brand perfumes……”</strong></p>
<p align="justify" class="body"><strong class="title3">Perfumes, Colognes, Gift Sets</strong><br>Delivering authentic top brand perfumes, colognes, cosmetics and gift sets has been and will remain our core focus over the coming years.</p>
<p align="justify" class="body">Can't find your product after years of searching? Ask us about it!</p>
<p align="justify" class="body">We carry a large line-up of designer fragrances, with over 3000 brand items in stock!</p>
<p align="justify" class="body">More importantly, we strive to maintain a large variety of fragrances, including hard-to-find brands. Our customers continue to be amazed at how our passion for perfumes and customer satisfaction allow us to find products they haven't been able to find in years! Its true! At Ace Gifts Plus, <br><strong>we've got what you're looking for!</strong></p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center"> </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0611/4257/files/vlueadded_large.jpg?428"></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center" class="title2"> </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center" class="title2">
<img alt="" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0611/4257/files/pricing_medium.jpg?425"><br><a name="5" id="5"></a>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left" class="body">
<div align="justify">Its rare to hear quality service and substantial savings in the same context – but that's a common occurrence at Ace Gifts Plus. We offer substantial savings to our customers, with up to 70% off retail prices! Friends have told friends and some of your friends have probably even told you <br>- that our low prices, coupled with the finest quality service produces<br>tremendous value and deep-pocket savings!</div>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left"> </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left" class="body">
<div align="justify">
<strong class="title3">How can we do it? Easy!</strong><br>We search the world for the best brands! Our impeccable service and substantial price savings produce value that you will not find anywhere else in the country! We guarantee it!* So what are you waiting for? We invite you to use our item catalogue. Start searching, start saving and find your favourite scent. At Ace Gifts Plus,<br>we've got what you're looking for!</div>
<div align="justify"></div>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center" class="title2 style1"><img alt="" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0611/4257/files/contacts_medium.jpg?426"></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center" class="body"></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="center" class="body"> </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left" class="body">
<p><strong>Mailing Address:</strong><br>24-1220 Ellesmere Road, Scarborough, ON, M1P2X5</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Telephone (Primary):</strong> 416-977-6181<br><strong>Telephone (Secondary):</strong> 416-977-3416<br><strong>Fax:</strong> 416-977-1945<br><strong>E-mail:</strong> <a href="mailto:sales@acegiftsplus.ca">sales@acegiftsplus.ca</a></p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left" class="body"> </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left" class="body">For any questions, comments or concerns regarding our products or services or this website, we invite you to email us at<a href="mailto:info@acegiftsplus.ca." class="style2"> info@acegiftsplus.ca.</a>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left" class="body"> </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left" class="body"><a href="http://acegiftsplus.ca/Harmeet_Business_Card.jpg"><strong> </strong></a></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left" class="body"> </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align="left" class="body">
<strong>C.N.E. (August)</strong><br>We also attend the annual trade exhibition at the C.N.E. every summer in the International Pavilion in Hall B. Look for us right by the International Stage, in the same spot every year for the past 10 years!</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<div></div>
<div></div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
